myadwall.com 2018-11-23

# MyAdWall - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

* * *

At MyAdWall, we strive to develop innovative services to better serve our users. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use MyAdWall's services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. 

The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. "Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address. 

**Anonymous Access**

Visitors can access the website home pages and browse site without disclosing personal data. 

**Automatic Data Collection**

MyAdWall may collect information from your computer, mobile phone or other access device. The information sent to us includes, but is not limited to, data on the pages you access, your computer IP address, referral data, device identifiers, the type of operating system you’re using, your location, mobile network information, standard web log data and other information. Web log data includes the browser type you’re using and traffic to and from our site to determine trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

**Data Collection and Purpose of Data Collection**

We may use the personal data supplied or provided by you to send you administrative emails, policy changes e-mails, T&C changes emails, e-mails regarding your account, etc.

Additionally, we may share personal data and demographic information we collect from you with our clients or partners in connection with promotions like market research surveys opportunities, offered by our clients or partners for several purposes, including, without limitation, facilitating your participation in a survey(s), fraud detection and prevention, copyright infringement, data validation, incentive or reward fulfillment (if applicable), identifying respondents for re-contact surveys, or communications, database matching, data append, coding, data segmentation, and/or developing data insights regarding survey participants, but not for marketing purposes. 

Access to collected personal data is available upon request. You can review your personal information at any time by opening a support ticket.We reserve the right to share your identity with others within the stipulations of data protection in an attempt to prevent further fraudulent activity. We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as identity verification services. 

**Children's Privacy**

MyAdWall does not knowingly collect personal data from individuals under the age of 13. Minors aged 13 to 18 are permitted to access the services of the site only by proper parental permission. It is the responsibility of the individual and the parent to ensure such permissions are obtained. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under the age of 13. If we are notified of such activity, we will verify the information and upon verification we will immediately remove such information from our servers. 

**Data collection and Disclosure**

MyAdWall collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, the date and time of your access and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services. 

Some of our services require you to register for an account. MyAdWall asks you for some personal information in order to create an account (typically your name, email address, and a password for your account) and we will use that information to provide the service. For certain services, such as our advertising programs, we may request Payment e-mail or ID, which we maintain in encrypted form on our server.

Except as set forth herein, MyAdWall does not disclose personal data to subsidiaries or other organizations without your permission or where it can reasonably be inferred from the circumstances that your consent to the disclosure to the third parties. MyAdWall tries to limit the information it provides to third parties to the information they need to help us to provide goods and services to you. 

**Cookies**

On 26 May 2011, the rules about cookies on websites changed. This site uses cookies. We have already set cookies which are essential for the operation of this site. By signing up you accept additional cookies from this site used to support optional features of the site or to gather anonymous usage statistics we use to improve the site. 

Upon your first visit to MyAdWall, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. 

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. MyAdWall does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people access our site. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some MyAdWall features or services may not function properly without cookies. 

**Access to your Personal Data**

Users may request access to their own specific personal information collected by us by opening a support ticket or by visiting your profile page (coming soon) . Access to personal information may require proof of identity. Access to personal data is provided without any fee or charge. Personal data may be challenged or updated and, where appropriate, data will be completed, erased, rectified or amended. MyAdWall reserves the right to refuse access to personal data. In such case, reasons will be given for refusal. 

You can close your account at MyAdWall by opening a support ticket. If you close your account, we will mark your account in our database as Closed / Banned but will keep your account information in our database. This is necessary to determine fraud or abuse of the site, by ensuring that persons who try to commit fraud or abuse of the site will not be able to avoid detection simply by closing their account and opening a new account. However, if you close your account, your personally-identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold to or shared with third parties, except as necessary to prevent fraud and assist law enforcement or as required by law. 

**Information sharing**

We will not sell or lease our members personal information to any other entity. We may share this information if that is required by a local Law Enforcement Agencies, survey partners, affiliate networks etc. We are not in the business of selling user's data and will not do so under any circumstances. 

**Accessing other Websites through MyAdWall**

This Privacy Policy is not applicable to other websites you access through MyAdWall. Therefore, any activity that user may carry out in connection with the linked websites must be governed by their own terms, conditions, legal notices and privacy policy, for which MyAdWall have no responsibility.We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collect personally identifiable information. 

**Changes to this Policy**

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page.
